[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "What did it feel like to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "it", "feel", "like", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "It sounded like a jet plane being on top of your roof and all your windows getting busted out.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "sounded", "like", "a", "jet", "plane", "being", "on", "top", "of", "your", "roof", "and", "all", "your", "windows", "getting", "busted", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "So what are you doing for accommodation?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "are", "you", "doing", "for", "accommodation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Right now, there was a lady that picked us up from the rescue center and he took us to her house last night.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "now", ",", "there", "was", "a", "lady", "that", "picked", "us", "up", "from", "the", "rescue", "center", "and", "he", "took", "us", "to", "her", "house", "last", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "And despite how awful the state of your home is, do you feel lucky, Ronna, given that other people were killed last night and so much devastation?", "question_tokens": ["And", "despite", "how", "awful", "the", "state", "of", "your", "home", "is", ",", "do", "you", "feel", "lucky", ",", "Ronna", ",", "given", "that", "other", "people", "were", "killed", "last", "night", "and", "so", "much", "devastation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "I feel very lucky because we're alive.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "very", "lucky", "because", "we", "'re", "alive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Ronna"], "TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Would you say this has been your toughest week personally in your job?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "say", "this", "has", "been", "your", "toughest", "week", "personally", "in", "your", "job", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "You know, Piers, I would say that it's been a challenging week, but in many ways, a week that I've enjoyed because I think that when a press secretary goes to the briefing room and there's a lot of intensity in the room and a lot of news, that, you know, it's inspiring reporters to ask hard questions.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "would", "say", "that", "it", "'s", "been", "a", "challenging", "week", ",", "but", "in", "many", "ways", ",", "a", "week", "that", "I", "'ve", "enjoyed", "because", "I", "think", "that", "when", "a", "press", "secretary", "goes", "to", "the", "briefing", "room", "and", "there", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "intensity", "in", "the", "room", "and", "a", "lot", "of", "news", ",", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "inspiring", "reporters", "to", "ask", "hard", "questions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"], "LOCATION": ["Benghazi"]}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "Can you comment on that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "comment", "on", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "That's part of the investigation led by the FBI that the president ordered immediately in the aftermath of the attacks in Benghazi.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "part", "of", "the", "investigation", "led", "by", "the", "FBI", "that", "the", "president", "ordered", "immediately", "in", "the", "aftermath", "of", "the", "attacks", "in", "Benghazi", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "Let me ask you, first of all, did you ever think you'd have to deal with three scandals like this at the same time?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "did", "you", "ever", "think", "you", "'d", "have", "to", "deal", "with", "three", "scandals", "like", "this", "at", "the", "same", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Well, I -- I dismiss the premise, the idea that these were scandals.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "--", "I", "dismiss", "the", "premise", ",", "the", "idea", "that", "these", "were", "scandals", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "Are you outraged by that as a journalist?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "outraged", "by", "that", "as", "a", "journalist", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "I very strongly believe, as does the president, in the need for the press to be able to pursue investigative journalism freely.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "very", "strongly", "believe", ",", "as", "does", "the", "president", ",", "in", "the", "need", "for", "the", "press", "to", "be", "able", "to", "pursue", "investigative", "journalism", "freely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Benghazi"]}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNPS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "Do you accept that and just on a general picture, how are you going to move on now and restore perhaps faith that some Americans have lost this week in your openness and honesty?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "accept", "that", "and", "just", "on", "a", "general", "picture", ",", "how", "are", "you", "going", "to", "move", "on", "now", "and", "restore", "perhaps", "faith", "that", "some", "Americans", "have", "lost", "this", "week", "in", "your", "openness", "and", "honesty", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "CC", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "Well, I'm not sure, again, you're concocting scandals here that don't exist, especially with regard to the Benghazi affair that was contrived by Republicans and I think has fallen apart largely this week.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "sure", ",", "again", ",", "you", "'re", "concocting", "scandals", "here", "that", "do", "n't", "exist", ",", "especially", "with", "regard", "to", "the", "Benghazi", "affair", "that", "was", "contrived", "by", "Republicans", "and", "I", "think", "has", "fallen", "apart", "largely", "this", "week", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "Is the belief of the investigators and the police now that the more they dig into this, the more likely it is that he just had these three women, that was what he concentrated on, that there may not be other crimes outside of that?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "the", "belief", "of", "the", "investigators", "and", "the", "police", "now", "that", "the", "more", "they", "dig", "into", "this", ",", "the", "more", "likely", "it", "is", "that", "he", "just", "had", "these", "three", "women", ",", "that", "was", "what", "he", "concentrated", "on", ",", "that", "there", "may", "not", "be", "other", "crimes", "outside", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "RBR", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "NNS", ",", "IN", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "IN", "EX", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "That's what it looks like so far.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "it", "looks", "like", "so", "far", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "IN", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Are they likely to speak in public any time soon, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "likely", "to", "speak", "in", "public", "any", "time", "soon", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Well, we all want that and there has been talk a couple of times that they're going to speak, they're going to speak, they're going to say something, and it never happened.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "all", "want", "that", "and", "there", "has", "been", "talk", "a", "couple", "of", "times", "that", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "speak", ",", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "speak", ",", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "say", "something", ",", "and", "it", "never", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "VBN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "And is Ariel Castro still cooperating with police, as he has been?", "question_tokens": ["And", "is", "Ariel", "Castro", "still", "cooperating", "with", "police", ",", "as", "he", "has", "been", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Well, they haven't questioned him in the last several days, although he is still in the same isolation in the cell, being watched 24/7 by the sheriff's department.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "have", "n't", "questioned", "him", "in", "the", "last", "several", "days", ",", "although", "he", "is", "still", "in", "the", "same", "isolation", "in", "the", "cell", ",", "being", "watched", "24/7", "by", "the", "sheriff", "'s", "department", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ariel Castro"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "Is there a growing sense as there was in the first few days, maybe, that this should all have been solved a long time ago?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "growing", "sense", "as", "there", "was", "in", "the", "first", "few", "days", ",", "maybe", ",", "that", "this", "should", "all", "have", "been", "solved", "a", "long", "time", "ago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "MD", "DT", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "There is a piece of that.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "is", "a", "piece", "of", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ":", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "First of all, looking at the Ariel Castro case since we last spoke, what is your assessment of where this investigation now is?", "question_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "looking", "at", "the", "Ariel", "Castro", "case", "since", "we", "last", "spoke", ",", "what", "is", "your", "assessment", "of", "where", "this", "investigation", "now", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "The investigation -- well, really, I was watching your show last night, it's really from the defense side, it's damage control.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "investigation", "--", "well", ",", "really", ",", "I", "was", "watching", "your", "show", "last", "night", ",", "it", "'s", "really", "from", "the", "defense", "side", ",", "it", "'s", "damage", "control", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ariel Castro"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "What would it mean legally, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "it", "mean", "legally", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "Well, from a legal perspective, the problem, if I was a defense attorney -- and the problem for the prosecution is the whole business of Mirandizing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "from", "a", "legal", "perspective", ",", "the", "problem", ",", "if", "I", "was", "a", "defense", "attorney", "--", "and", "the", "problem", "for", "the", "prosecution", "is", "the", "whole", "business", "of", "Mirandizing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "How you feeling?", "question_tokens": ["How", "you", "feeling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "I'm good.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Should all the people who have had any involvement in targeting Tea Party groups just on the supposition that they're Tea Party activists -- should they all be fired?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "all", "the", "people", "who", "have", "had", "any", "involvement", "in", "targeting", "Tea", "Party", "groups", "just", "on", "the", "supposition", "that", "they", "'re", "Tea", "Party", "activists", "--", "should", "they", "all", "be", "fired", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", ":", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "Again, I'm not going to speak for the executive branch.", "answer_tokens": ["Again", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "speak", "for", "the", "executive", "branch", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "If it turns out they were, if more e-mails come out and the State Department, for political reasons, were trying to remove the fact this may have been a terrorist attack, should heads roll at the State Department?", "question_tokens": ["If", "it", "turns", "out", "they", "were", ",", "if", "more", "e-mails", "come", "out", "and", "the", "State", "Department", ",", "for", "political", "reasons", ",", "were", "trying", "to", "remove", "the", "fact", "this", "may", "have", "been", "a", "terrorist", "attack", ",", "should", "heads", "roll", "at", "the", "State", "Department", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "NNS", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Again, I'm not going to speak for the executive branch.", "answer_tokens": ["Again", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "speak", "for", "the", "executive", "branch", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["State Department", "State Department"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Should he?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "Yeah, I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "You haven't set a date for your wedding yet, have you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "n't", "set", "a", "date", "for", "your", "wedding", "yet", ",", "have", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Well, I'm not going to make news there.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "make", "news", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Penn, how are you doing?", "question_tokens": ["Penn", ",", "how", "are", "you", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "I'm doing very well, thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "doing", "very", "well", ",", "thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Feeling bullish?", "question_tokens": ["Feeling", "bullish", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "I suppose so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "suppose", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130516pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "As an American, somebody who pays a lot of taxes, I would imagine, like I do, how do you feel about the IRS turning all political, going off to people for their political believes?", "question_tokens": ["As", "an", "American", ",", "somebody", "who", "pays", "a", "lot", "of", "taxes", ",", "I", "would", "imagine", ",", "like", "I", "do", ",", "how", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "the", "IRS", "turning", "all", "political", ",", "going", "off", "to", "people", "for", "their", "political", "believes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "You know, this is one of those things that just breaks my heart.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "this", "is", "one", "of", "those", "things", "that", "just", "breaks", "my", "heart", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["IRS"]}}]